commerceinterface.com 2012-06-01

# Privacy Policy

This website is owned and operated by CommerceInterface, Inc. This Privacy Policy details what information we collect when you visit, browse and use [http://www.commerceinterface.com](http://www.commerceinterface.com/) (known as the “website” or “site”) or [http://app.commerceinterface.com](http://app.commerceinterface.com/) (known as the “e-commerce platform”) and how we use the information we collect. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.

### I. Collection of Information

You can browse, view and visit the site without revealing any personal information about yourself or your company. As you browse our site, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. Once you create an account, you will no longer be anonymous to us. Upon the creation of an account with us, we will collect and store the following personal information:

  * Email address, physical contact information and financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * Transactional information based on your activities on the site and through our e-commerce platform;
  * Information about your selling history; and
  * Other information from your interaction with the site and the e-commerce platform, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the site, IP address and standard web log information.

### II. Marketing

We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your consent. We may market products and/or services to you that we believe may be of interest to you.

### III. Use of Information

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to communicate with you, facilitate the purpose for which you contacted us and improve our services. You agree we may use your personal information to:

  * Provide the services and support you request;
  * Customize, measure and improve our services; and
  * Tell you about products and/or services which may be of interest to you.

### IV. Disclosure

We may disclose your information to our staff and to third parties involved in any transaction through the e-commerce platform. We may disclose your information in response to process of law or to comply with governmental or administrative inquiries or orders.

### V. Protection

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system.

### VI. Third Party Websites

The site or the e-commerce platform may contain links or references to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites even if you access them using links from our site. Your use of third party websites is entirely at your own risk. We make no representation or warranty as to the effectiveness, quality, legitimacy or data protections of any third party website.

### VII. Account Protection

Your username and password controls your access to the CommerceInterface e-commerce platform. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your password to anyone. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should notify us immediately and change your password.
